天呐 娘亲啊
Oh, my god. Mom.
派对就在离家不远处
The party is like around the block.
我就出去两小时
I'll be gone for two hours.
那可是两小时啊 能用来学多少东西啊
Yeah. That is two hours you could've spent studying.
我整个周末都在看书看书看书
I had been studying all weekend.
没有和人出去玩 没有和人打电话
No friends, no phone.
跟一堆书在一起 我快成寂寞姐了
Just me, alone with books.
我快成艾丽克斯第二了
I feel like Alex.
有书作陪 寂寞都是浮云
You're never alone when you have books.
真的吗 你想让我变成那副样子吗
Really? Is that what you want me to turn into?
乖 听我讲 你都高考临头了
Sweetheart, listen to me. This is the SATs, okay?
不是小打小闹的科学小测验
It is not some stupid science quiz.
嘿 如果科学小测验是小打小闹
Hey, if science quizzes are so stupid,
你们还把我的高分试卷贴到冰箱上显摆
Why do you put mine up on the refrigerator?
那是因为我们觉得你很可怜
Because we feel sorry for you,
只有书和你做朋友
'cause books are your friends.
她昨晚根本没在看书
Yeah, she wasn't studying last night.
她一直和人视频聊天来着
She was video-chatting the whole time.
-闭嘴 - 我就知道你会这样
- Shut up! - I knew it.
-我就知道 -你居然打我小报告
- I knew it. - You are such a tattletale!
孩子们 不要吵了 我想
Girls, take it down a notch, because I ...
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
我们家三个女人这唱的又是哪出戏啊
What's the hot topic on "The View" today, ladies?
老爸 能不能劳烦你劝劝老妈
Dad, can you just please tell mom
放我两小时假 让我去参加个派对
that I can take a two-hour break and go to a party?
不好意思 美女 我才不想趟这浑水
No, ma'am. I'm not stepping into that one.
别拉我跟你老妈对着干
We're not playing good cop/mom.
来了
I got it.
-你好 -是你叫的水管工么
- Hello. - You call for a plumber?
呃 没有 我们没叫
Uh, no, we did not.
别 别 我们叫了 叫了
Oh, yes, We did, we did.
水管工 你好
Plumber, hi. Yeah.
出问题的管道就在楼上 谢谢了
Um, it's right up at the top of the stairs. Thank you.
有必要吗 克莱尔
Really, Claire?
难道我没跟你讲过我会修浴缸吗
But didn't I tell you I'd fix the tub?
是的 亲爱的 你讲过
Yes, honey, you did.
当年我还怀着卢克的时候你就承诺过
And I think I was pregnant with Luke at the time.
这么说可不公平
That is not fair.
在家里你叫我干啥我就干啥
I've done everything you've asked me to do around here.
我都把楼梯修好了 不是吗 看看多结实
I fixed the step, didn't I? Look how solid it is!
我可以在上面像秀兰·邓波尔
I'm like Shirley Temple
和那个黑人小伙一样跳舞
and that black guy!
那黑人小伙叫比尔·罗宾逊
Bill "Bojangles" Robinson.
对 就是比尔·罗宾逊
Bill "Bojangles" Robinson!
我先说的
I said it first!
就是这里出问题了
So, this is the problem.
水龙头一直在漏水
Uh, faucet just keeps leaking.
对的 垫圈裂了
Yeah, it's a cracked washer --
我清楚得很
If I know my washers.
一直在滴滴答答滴水
And it's, uh, it's been leaking a little water.
恩 很可能是垫圈裂了
Yeah, could be a washer,
也搞不好是阀门或者是水管裂了
a cracked valve, a stripped pipe.
我觉得虽然我不是专业水管工
Well, I guess I'm not a professional plumber,
但我在那浴缸呆过很长时间
but I have spent a huge amount of time in that tub.
我可以从从经验上
I can tell you from experience,
至少是躺在里面的感觉....
or at least what it feels like in there --
嗷 太好了 你回来了
Oh, good. You're back.
你说我是扮成
I need you to help settle a spat
小铁匠还是扫烟囱的人呢
between our blacksmith and the chimney sweep.
淡定 我花了20分钟才找到这件拉风的斗篷
Be nice. It took me 20 minutes to find my opera cloak.
还是难以置信 你根本不必租这些的啊
I still can't believe. You didn't have to rent any of that.
拜托
Oh, please.
你知道它们有多物超所值吗
Do you know how many times this has paid for itself?
是吗
Has it?
我们的老朋友佩珀
Well, our friend Pepper
很喜欢开主题派对
loves to throw theme parties.
是的 他超爱
Yes, he does,
本周末是他的首次年度
And this weekend is his first annual
"奥斯卡·王尔德疯狂餐会"
"Oscar Wilde and Crazy Brunch."
我们还没恢复元气呢
We're still recovering
他上次的主题烧烤会可把我们雷的不轻
from his "Studio 54th of July" barbecue.
一开始这些主题派对还是很有趣的
They were fun at first.
但是后来就变成了个负担
But they have become a lot of work.
你必须换装
You have to dress in costume.
还必须玩角色扮演
You have to assume a character.
我 我真不敢相信你居然跟他约会过
I -- I can't believe you ever dated him.
就一次
One date.
都上世纪的事儿了
It was the '90s.
当时戴安娜王妃刚刚去世
We'd just lost Princess Di.
我觉得世界天崩地裂
I was at sea.
嗷 小卡 我们能不能
Oh, Cam, can we just...
我们能不能不要去啦
Can we please cancel?
人家也不想去呀
I wish we could.
但是他还怨念着我们逾越节那次没有去
But you know he's still mad at us for missing Passover.
好吧 我懂的
Oh. Right.
"逾越节狂欢夜"那次吗
"Seder-day night Fever"?
去换身衣服 往脸上扑点儿香粉
Just go get dressed and powdered.
噢
Ohh.
佩珀完成了不可能完成的任务
Pepper has done the impossible!
他成功让俩基佬开始厌恶早午餐
He's made two gay men hate brunch.
你不如直接
You know, it might be easier
把浓缩咖啡倒到糖罐里
just to pour the espresso right in the sugar.
天天唠叨
Every morning.
杰 你怎么穿成这样
Jay, what are you wearing?
你不能这样去教堂
You can't go to church like that.
那就甭去了 我待会儿打高尔夫去
Well, that settles it, then. I'm going golfing.
你又要逃避做礼拜
You're gonna miss church again?
上个礼拜天
Last sunday,
你说你要去办公室
you said that you had to go to the office.
上上个礼拜 你说你要去和朋友吃早饭
The week before, you had breakfast with a friend.
上上上个礼拜 你觉得你感冒了
And before that, you thought you had a cold.
结果压根儿不是感冒
That turned out not to be a cold.
那是因为我休养好了
Because I babied it.
你不用跟我们废话
You don't have to convince us.
-你跟他讲去 谁 -上帝吗
- You have to convince him. - Who, god?
-他老人家是我铁哥们儿呢 -你怎么知道
- Me and god are good! - How would you know?
听着 你在教堂里感知上帝 这很好
Look, you feel god in church, which is great.
但我从自然中感知上帝 大自然也是上帝的杰作
I feel god out in nature, amongst his works.
你下个礼拜会去教堂吗
Are you gonna go to church next week?
看情况吧
We'll see.
那就是说不去咯
I know what "we'll see" means.
如果你再也不想去了 就勇敢说出来嘛
If you're done with church, just say it.
-我再也不会去教堂了 -闭嘴 不要乱说
- I'm done with church. - Don't say that!
听着 我不会再去教堂了
Look -- I'm not going to church anymore.
又不是什么世界末日
It's not the end of the world.
别搁这事上小题大做
Let's not make a big deal out --
靠
Hell...
啊 啊 地震了
Aah. Aah. Earthquake!
地震啦
Terremoto!
我们走 我们走 曼尼 走 杰
Vamos, vamos, Manny! Vamos, Jay!
快点 杰
Come on, Jay!
孩子们
Girls?!
噢 神啊 神啊
Oh, god. Oh, god.
完了
Okay.
这边 门卡住了
This is -- this is stuck!
我们会死在这的 会死滴
We're gonna die! we're gonna die!
最好别
We better not.
如果人们发现我们死时穿成这样儿
If they find us in these outfits,
又得有人借机攻击同志群体了
it's gonna be very bad for the gays.
-克莱尔 -我们没事
- Clair - We're okay!
-爸 -卢克
- Dad? - Luke!
宝贝儿子
Buddy.
你没事吧
You okay?
那东西差点砸到我
That thing almost fell on me!
我刚就坐那儿
I was sitting there,
差这么点砸到我脑袋
and it came this close to my head!
好了 你没事了
It's all right. You're okay.
你没受伤
You didn't get hurt.
我可不想在这儿等着被受伤呢
Well, I'm not gonna wait around here until I do.
哎...呀呀
O... kay.
直挺挺地倒下了
Wow!
痛痛飞 痛痛飞
That is a doozy.
你们没事吧
Hey, are you guys okay?
我们没事 你们呢
Yeah, we're fine. You?
没事
We're fine.
那真是...
That was really...
稍等
Oh, wait. Hold on.
喂
Hello?
米奇 你们没事吧
Mitch, are you okay?
没事 我们没事
We're okay. We're okay.
菲尔和克莱尔呢
And Phil and Claire?
我刚正跟他们通话呢
Uh, I'm on the other line with them right now.
稍等
One second.
喂
Hello?
见鬼 菲尔挂了
Oh, shoot, we lost Phil.
菲尔挂了吗
We lost Phil?!
菲尔挂了?
We lost Phil?
喂
Hello?
这可好 歌洛莉亚也没了
Great. Now Gloria's gone.
歌洛莉亚也魂归西天了?
Gloria's gone, too?
天啊
Ohh!
嘿 歌洛莉亚
Hey, Gloria.
感谢上帝 菲尔 你还活着
Ay, dios meo, Phil, you're alive!
我当然没死
Yeah, of course I'm alive.
暂时而已
For now.
几个月来 克莱尔一直咬着我不放
For months, Claire has been after me
喋喋不休
and dogging me
"把储藏柜固定到墙上"
"Anchor the cabinet to the wall."
"要是地震了怎么办"
"What if we have an earthquake?"
"屋里可有孩子"
"We've got kids in the house."
废话不断
Blah blah blah.
最终我被逼无奈
So it finally reached the point where I had no choice,
只能挽起袖子 骗她说我搞定了
but to just roll up my sleeves and tell her I did it.
菲尔
Phil!
老爸 上这来
Dad, get up here!
来了 开什么玩笑 我刚修好的
On my way -- seriously, I just fixed that!
哈利
Haley...
怎么回事
What's wrong?
老妈被困在里面了
Mom's stuck!
你们在里面还好吧
You okay in there?
我们没事
We're fine.
门卡住了
The door is jammed.
-那我们一起用力 -好的
- Uh...well, let's -- let's try this together, okay? - Okay.
我推 你拉
Um, I'm gonna push, you pull.
行 数三声
Okay. On three.
不管用
Aah! nothing!
该死
Oh, damn!
其实是这样的
Okay, here's the thing.
我可没推 相反我有点往外拉
I wasn't pushing. In fact, I was pulling a little.
我深知
It dawned on me
只要克莱尔困在浴室里
that as long as Claire was stuck in the bathroom,
我就有时间把储藏柜固定到墙上
I'd have time to anchor the cabinet to the wall.
可以这样说
It's like they say
有时 上帝关上了一道门
sometimes when god closes a door,
他故意关紧 这样你老婆就出不来
he closes it so hard that your wife can't get out.
别慌 我会救你出来
So, don't panic! I'm gonna get you out!
我去拿点工具
I'm just gonna go get some tools!
用铁橇吧 假设你有的话
Get a crowbar if you have one!
你那话什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
说我是个连铁撬都没有的孬白脸是吧
Like I'm some dandy who doesn't have a crowbar?
这可是你自己说的
Well, you did just use the word "dandy."
"孬白脸"可是15世纪的矿工所创作的词
"dandy" is a term coined by miners in the 15th century.
菲尔
Phil?
少废话 把我们弄出去
Just get us out of here.
老爸 把她弄出来要多长时间
Dad, how long is it gonna take to get her out of there?
非常久
Long time.
宝贝们 别担心
Oh, honey. Don't worry.
妈妈会很快出来 别紧张
Mommy is gonna be out soon. Don't panic.
慢着
Wait a minute.
站住 死丫头 你别想趁机溜去派对
Wait a minute. You're not going to that party, young lady.
不 我没想去派对
No, I'm not going to the party.
我只是下楼罢了
I'm just going downstairs.
下楼还背包
With your purse?
拜托
Come on.
就这次为我掩护下
Just cover for me this one time, and I...
以后你想去哪 姐都开车送
I'll drive you wherever you want.
我想去"宽容博物馆"
I want to go to the Museum of Tolerance.
行 宽容嘛 有什么难的
Fine. How far is Tolerance?
你们的诡计 我听的清清楚楚
I can hear the two of you scheming out there!
有本事你离开家试试看
Don't you dare leave this house!
你简直就是一个疯婆娘
Ohh, why do you have to be such a psycho control freak?!
行啊 给我听着
Okay, you know what?
就冲那句 我关你一礼拜紧闭
Just for that, you are grounded one week!
真是教导有方
Oh, that's good parenting!
有你的 两个礼拜
Okay. Two weeks.
还想翻倍吗 接着说啊
Want to double it?! keep talking!
啦啦啦啦啦
Blah blah blah blah blah!
行 四个礼拜 四！！
Fine! four weeks! four!
接着翻啊 干脆十个礼拜算了
Double it again and make it 10 weeks!
天啊
Oh, my god!
瞧你蠢的 再怎么翻也翻不到十倍吧
Do you not hear how much you need to study?!
米奇尔 快点 我们要迟到了
Mitchell, come on. We're gonna be late.
真不敢相信还是要去
Ohh, I can't believe we have to do this.
拜托 地震之后
Come on, after the earthquake,
大家都这样打扮不是挺好的吗
it might be nice to be around similarly dressed people.
简直毫无... 哦对了 地震
That makes no... the earthquake!
没错 没错
Okay. Okay. Yes.
这可是个绝佳借口
Yes. This -- okay. This is the perfect excuse.
为什么 我们有惊无险
Why? We're fine.
确实 但佩珀不知情
Yeah, but Pepper doesn't know that.
你只需告知他
You'll just tell him
我们要进行灾后重建工作
that we have some damage we have to deal with.
-为什么是我 -因为以前都是我放他鸽子
- Why me? - Because I'm the one that always cancels.
-喂 -别给我 我不跟他讲
- Hello. - No. Don't hand me that I will not talk to him.
我可不会说谎 拿远点
I'm a bad liar. Do not hand me that.
他现在接通了
He is on the phone right now.
快接 该你上了
Pick up. You are doing it!
我听见人声了 喂
I think somebody's talking. Hello?
嗨 佩珀
Hi! Pepper!
嗨 听我说 嗨 嘿
Listen -- hi. Hey.
我是卡梅隆 你那边情况怎么样
It's Cameron. How are you doing over there?
很好
Great.
这地震
Well, the earthquake.
嗯 这边很严重 非常严重
Yeah, it was huge here. Huge.
因而 显然我们
So, obviously, we're not,
我们没法过来了
we're not gonna be able to make it.
-为什么 -碎了些餐具
- Why not? - Well, some dishes broke.
可以以后再扫的嘛
You can sweep them up later.
是的 没错 我想
And, uh, well, yeah, I guess --
我想我们是可以以后再扫的
I guess we could sweep those up, um, later.
我们的 我们的衣帽架
Our, uh, our -- our hat rack.
-我们的衣帽架倒在窗户上了 -衣帽架
- Our hat rack fell through the window. - Hat rack?
是啊 我们真的有个衣帽架的
Well, yeah, we do have a hat rack.
我们认为这会迫使我们经常戴帽子
We thought it would force us to wear our hats more.
事实也的确如此
And it did.
我们这里还水漫金山寺
And there's water damage.
到处都是水
There's water everywhere.
书架砸中了米奇尔的腿
A bookshelf fell on Mitchell's leg.
米奇尔受伤了 佩珀
Mitchell's hurt, Pepper.
米奇尔伤得相当严重
Mitchell's hurt real bad.
我这就过来
I'm coming right over.
不 不劳您大驾了
No, you don't need to come over.
-我马山来 -佩珀 不要
- I'm coming! - Pepper, no!
他要过来了
He's coming over.
看见没 人家说了会紧张的嘛
See? Kind of panicked.
你确实很紧张 小卡
You did panic, Cam.
你简直惊慌失措
You paniced real bad.
你还要去打高尔夫吗
You're still going golfing?!
上帝都给你暗示了 杰
God sent you a sign, Jay!
什么 地震吗 你开什么玩笑
What, the earthquake? You got to be kidding me.
你说你再也不会去教堂了
You say that you're never going to church again,
接着大地就报复性地晃动
and the ground shakes with a vengeance.
我来证明给你看
I'll prove it to you.
上帝啊 你要是不爽我打高尔夫的话
God, if you have a problem with me golfing,
就给我个暗示
send me a sign!
比如 让闪电劈死我吧
I mean, throw in a little lightning!
小宇宙大爆发吧
Put on a show!
不准那样跟上帝讲话
Don't talk to god like that!
相信我 要是上帝看我不爽的话
Trust me, if god had a problem with me,
他不用摇晃整个城市来警告我
he would let me know without shaking the whole city.
他可以指向更明确一些
He would be a little more specific.
我懒得跟你吵
I'm not gonna argue with you.
我可不想气自己
I don't want to get upset.
曼尼 我们走
Vlmanos, Manny.
-我今天想翘一天 - 什么
- I think I'm gonna skip it today. - What?!
我觉得杰说的很对 上帝存在于自然当中
I like what Jay said about god being in nature.
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
别听他滴
Don't listen to him.
他已经时日无多了
His days are numbered!
妈妈 想想看 他说的确实有点道理
Think about it, mom. It makes sense.
上帝创造了草木
God made the trees and the grass.
可他并没有盖教堂啊
He didn't make that church.
但是他创造了盖教堂的人
But he made the people that make the church,
你让老娘很火大 我们走
and you're making me angry! Vlmanos.
就这一周
Just one week.
我能跟你去打高尔夫吗
Can I go golfing with you?
反正我也得找个
Well, I'm probably gonna have
扛球袋的拉丁裔小孩儿
a Latino kid carry my clubs anyway.
肥水不流外人田
Might as well be you.
好吧 我才不在乎呢 去吧
Fine! See what I care! go!
曼尼 回去换衣服
Manny. Go change.
对不起了 老娘 您大人不记小人过
Sorry, mom. Hope you understand.
出去一起玩可能会增进我俩的情感呢
Probably good for us to spend a little time together.
你们一起永不超生去吧
You're gonna spend eternity together!
该死
Ohh. Damn it!
我猜那也是上帝干的
I suppose that was god, too!
我不知道谁干滴 但是大快人心
I don't know who did it, but it makes me happy.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
哥们儿
Hey, buddy.
我再检查一下这些皮带
Oh, just double-checking these straps.
这条是多余的
This is an extra.
这些小玩意儿救了你的命
These babies saved your life.
因为它们 储藏柜纹丝未动
That's why this cabinet barely moved.
柜子直接倒在了沙发上
It fell all the way to the couch.
差点砸死我
It almost killed me.
不 不是这样的
No, it didn't.
这储藏柜根本没动
This cabinet barely moved.
不过是角度产生的视感错觉罢了
That's just perspective playing tricks on your mind.
从我这个方位看过去 我的拇指比你的头还大
Like if I hold up my thumb, it looks bigger than your head.
不 才没有 它好小
No, it doesn't. It looks tiny.
你得从这边看
You have to look at it from over here.
我怎么从那边看我的自己的头
How can I look at my head from over there?
菲尔
Phil?
你何不躺下
Why don't you just lie down?
我去确认下你老妈是不是还被困在里面
I got to make sure your mom's still stuck.
这样她 我会把她救出来的
So she -- I can get her out.
别睡着了
Don't fall asleep.
很抱歉耽搁 我日...
Sorry that took -- you filthy...
很抱歉耽搁了这么久
Sorry that took so long!
我准备将门把手撬下来 好吗
I'm gonna go ahead and just take off the doorknob, okay?
好的
Okay!
开始了
There we go.
这 该死
That's -- oh, damn!
什么 怎么回事
What? What happened?
我拿错螺丝刀了
I, uh, brought the wrong screwdriver,
我马上回来
So I'll be right back!
好吧 不过快点 菲尔
All right, but hurry up, Phil!
我尽力而为 克莱尔
Doing my best, Claire!
别回她话 小心关你禁闭
Oh, don't talk back, dad! She'll just ground you!
三十二个礼拜了 死丫头片子
That's 32 weeks, young lady!
我之前说的是十六个礼拜 对吧
I was at 16 before, right?
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
等你有这么个青春期的女儿再来评价我
Don't judge me until you've had a teenage girl.
我有四个
I've had four of them.
天啊 你怎么熬过来的
God, how did you survive that?
女儿还不好对付
Girls were a piece of cake.
让我头疼的是儿子
It was the boy.
他脸上的每一个表情
Every look on his face,
他每个愚蠢的决定
every stupid decision he made.
坐在那儿像白痴一样嚼东西
The way he sat there, chewing his food like an idiot.
然后我突然明白这孩子为何使我这么抓狂
And then it hit me why this kid drove me so crazy.
他就是当年的我
He's me.
那她就更应该听我的话了
Well, all the more reason she should listen to me.
我可以避免她重蹈我的覆辙
I can stop her from making the same mistakes.
你当年听妈妈的话吗
Did you listen to your mother?
怎么可能
Ohh, god no.
不过 你要知道我是有原因的
But, you know, I had a reason.
那女人简直就是个疯婆...
That woman was a psycho control...
...娘
freak.
老妈
Hey, mom.
我给你们弄了些苏打水
I brought you some soda.
不过我找不到吸管
But I couldn't find any straws,
所以你们得像小猫一样舔着喝
So you'll have to drink it like cats.
谢谢你 卢克
Oh! Thank you, Luke!
那是我的心肝宝贝
That's my sweetie.
我本来想给你带酒的
I was going to bring you wine,
不过你昨晚把那一大瓶都喝完了
but you finished the big bottle last night.
好了 你可以走了
Okay. Off you go.
拿好这个 没问题吧 小子
Hold this, will you, kid?
没问题
Sure.
以前都是米奇尔给我当球童
You know, Mitchell used to caddy for me.
当然 他大多时候是在追蝴蝶
Of course, he spent most of his time chasing butterflies.
我不会那么做的
You won't catch me doing that.
真乖
Good for you.
我害怕蝴蝶
I'm terrified of them.
是吗
Huh.
看 那一杆堪称完美
Look at that. That's a perfect shot.
我还是用的烂球杆打的
And I hit that with a bent club.
你不担心会惹上麻烦吗
So you're not worried about getting in trouble?
不害怕上帝会找你茬吗
You know, with god?
我想他有比这更重要的事要操心
Oh, I think he's got bigger things on his plate.
那你也不担心会下地狱吗
So you're not worried about hell?
告诉你点小秘密 孩子
Let me let you in on a little secret, kid.
世上根本没有地狱
There is no hell.
真的吗
Seriously?
没有地狱吗
No hell?
真他妈太棒了
That's fantastic!
那所有的人都会去天堂喽
So everyone just goes to heaven?
对 这个话题到此为止
Yep. End of story.
连坏人也能去天堂吗
Even bad people?
对 他们 他们坏人
Yeah, they're -- they're --
分配到了别的地方 懂吗
they're in another section, see?
上帝都安排好了的
They got this thing figured out.
现在我能打了球了吧
Can I hit this?
该死
Damn it.
你让我分心了
You distracted me.
我什么也没说啊
I didn't say anything!
我能听到你内心的想法
I could hear you thinking.
我正在想你说的那个
I'm thinking about this heaven of yours
到处都是坏人的天堂
that's full of bad people.
不全是坏人 只有很少的一拨人
Not full. The tiniest fraction.
他们都被关起来了
They're walled in.
万一他们越狱怎么办
What if they break out?
有一个火焰湖包围他们呢
They're surrounded by a lake of fire.
天堂里竟然还有火焰湖
They are fiery lakes in heaven?
那简直就跟地狱一样了
This is turning into hell.
谁说不是呢
Tell me about it.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?!
你都告诉佩珀打碎了很多碟子
Well, you promised Pepper broken dishes,
所以...
so...
我要打碎这个
I'm breaking this.
不 不要打碎我的青蛙奖杯
No! Not my frog!
我知道你觉得这很不入眼
I know you think it's tacky,
但是 这是我第一次参加4-H夏令营
but I happened to have won this at my first 4-H summer camp
在吆喝比赛里偶然得的
in a hollerin' contest.
如果你撒谎撒的好点
Well, we wouldn't have to break anything
我们就不用打破这么多东西了
if you were a better liar.
如果你是想让我感到愧疚
If you're trying to make me feel bad
因为我撒谎撒的没你好
about not being as good a liar as you --
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
你还说衣帽架砸到窗户上了 忘啦
A hat rack fell through the window, remember?
1...2...3
One...Two...Three!
米奇尔 停
Mitchell, wait!
我...我做不到 我退出
I-I-I can't do this. I quit.
撒这些谎 你可能觉得没什么
You might be comfortable with all this lying,
可我觉得很不舒服
but I'm not.
拜托 你别这么装B好吧
Oh, please. Where was all this conscience
那次我可是靠撒谎才把咱俩弄进头等舱的
when I got us into the first-class lounge at the airport
而你却忙着跟安吉拉·兰斯伯里唠嗑
and you chewed Angela Lansbury's ear off.
你知道你是哪种人吗
You know what you are?
你就像是暴徒的老婆
You're like a mob wife.
你看不起自己老公 鄙视他做事的方法
You look down at me and my ways,
但是你却屁颠屁颠地
but you're happy to wear the mink coat
乐于坐享其成
that fell off the back of the truck!
你竟敢这么说我
How dare you?
不用说了 我知道
I know. I know.
真的震得很严重
It really hit us bad.
不是
No.
我只是一直都很惊讶 这个地方是有多小啊
I'm just always surprised how small this place is.
佩珀 你没必要离开派对
Pepper, you didn't have to leave your party
特意来看我们
to come check on us.
顺便说一下 戏服真不错
Great costume, by the way.
这不是我的戏服
This isn't my costume.
这才不是我的工作服 干苦力时穿的
I just threw this on to help you clean up.
没能去你的派对...
Well, about your party...
别心怀愧疚了啦
Oh, don't worry about canceling.
至少你们还有个理由
At least you have an excuse.
不像史蒂文和斯蒂芬
Unlike Steven and Stefan.
他们说他们感冒了
They said they had the flu.
但刚才我还看见他们骑情侣车出去了
Meantime, I just saw them out riding their bicycle.
佩珀 他们太不厚道了
Oh, Pepper, that is horrible.
我去给你弄杯鸡尾酒
I-I'm gonna make you a cocktail.
亲爱的 不用这么麻烦
Oh, honey. Don't go to any trouble.
给我弄杯葡萄干酒就行
I'll just have a Kir Royale.
我是说 我的天啊
I mean, my god,
如果他们不想来我的派对
if they didn't want to come to my party,
直接说嘛
just say it.
我是个大人了 我能扛得住
I'm a big boy. I can take it.
既然你提起来了 佩珀...
Well, since you brought it up, Pepper...
其实我们也不想去你的派对
We didn't want to come to your party, either.
什么
What?
你知道我们是爱你的
Well, you know we love you,
但是这么多年以来 真的成了一种负担
but they've just gotten to be so much work over the years, and...
我们没有黑醋栗甜酒了
we're all out of cassis.
我受不了了
I can't bear it!
我去给你弄杯贝利尼
I will make you a Bellini.
大家都放我鸽子
Everybody canceled on me!
现在你们两个也这样
And now you two!
15年来
For 15 years,
我散尽钱财 心力交瘁
I have killed myself setting a community standard
做出各种新奇主题的早午餐
with my fanciful themed brunches
给大家制造一个和谐的社区氛围
mounted at great personal expense.
很明显 我一直都是个傻帽儿
Well, clearly, I've been a fool.
佩珀 没人喜欢你的早午餐
No one likes your brunches, Pepper.
没人待见你
No one likes you.
你会孤独终老
You're gonna die alone!
在棕榈泉外的西班牙复古风中驾鹤西去
In a quaint Spanish revival outside of Palm Springs...
或者奎因塔
Or La Quinta.
我做了回恶人
Yeah. I told him.
恩 看出来了
Yeah. Yeah, I puzzled that out.
我就是不太明白天堂里坏人待的地方
I just don't understand this bad section of heaven.
要是他们把你送错了地方怎么办
What if they send you to the wrong place?
有时候资料会填错
They make mistakes with paperwork sometimes.
去年我就被错误安排在女性生理健康课上
I was put in a girls' health class last year
结果看到了非常可怕滴教育片
and had to watch a very disturbing movie.
淡定
Calm down.
整个上午 别再想什么
Instead of thinking all morning
天堂应该是什么样儿的啊
about what heaven's gonna look like,
不应该是什么样儿的啊 谁该在哪里啊
what it's not gonna look like, who's where.
如果天堂真的存在的话
If there even is a heaven.
我们为什么不专心享受
Why don't we just concentrate
我们眼前 又美丽又悠闲的一天呢
on this beautiful, carefree day that's in front of us?
我宁愿想想你刚才说的那些
I'd rather concentrate on something you just said.
难道天堂真的不存在吗
There might not even be a heaven?
我不知道
I don't know!
可是今天早晨你看起来自信满满
You seemed pretty sure of yourself this morning.
那人死了以后会怎么样呢
So what happens after you die?
一切都是浮云吗
There's just nothing?
听着 我就说了一件小事
Look, you're focusing too much
你却揪着不放到现在
on one little thing that I said.
那些都只是我的直觉好吗
It was just a hunch, okay?
直觉
A hunch?
我没去教堂 就因为你的直觉
I'm skipping church based on a hunch?!
好了 不要吓我 孩子
All right, don't freak out on me here, kid.
你无耻地玩弄了人家幼小的灵魂...
You're playing pretty fast and loose with my soul.
听着 我要你忘了
Listen. I want you to forget everything
我说的一切 好吗
that I said, okay?
杰 有些事情是刻骨铭心的
Some things can't be forgotten, Jay.
你知道什么叫月经吗
Do you know what menstruation is?
小爷我可一清二楚
Because I do.
搞定
Perfect.
-嘿 -你在干嘛
- Hey! - W-what are you doing?
你不是该把老妈从浴室里弄出来吗
Aren't you supposed to be getting mom out of the bathroom?
我正是在干这个啊
That is what I was doing.
这个 这个柜子
This c-- this cabinet...
-正是问题所在 -怎么说
- Was the problem. - How?
这个柜子很沉
Yeah. It's very heavy,
而且是妥妥地固定在墙上的
and because it was properly anchored to the wall,
所以就有了一些连锁反应
there's sort of a ripple effect.
就是说
It was...
它压住了地板的一边
pulling part of the floor down...
另一边就被抬起来了
and then pushing part of the floor up,
然后这浴室的门就
using the bathroom door --
拜托别告发我
Please don't tell on me.
我不知道我现在是谁了
I don't know who I am anymore!
我是谁
Who am I?!
我就是个笑话
I'm a joke!
这就是我
That's who.
-才不是 -不是
- No. - No.
你不是个笑话
You're not a joke.
你是佩珀·萨尔茨曼
You're Pepper Saltzman.
我觉得我还是走吧
I think I better just go.
就算我在回去的路上发生什么意外
If anything terrible should happen,
你们也无须被迫去参加我的追悼会
don't feel an obligation to attend my memorial.
纽约和洛杉矶的都不用参加
New york or L.A..
佩珀
Pepper?
佩珀 你都没让我把话说完
Pepper, you -- you didn't let me finish.
我们不想去参加你的派对只是因为
The reason we didn't want to come to your party is...
米奇尔
Mitchell?
是不是啊你
Seriously?
-谁是暴徒之妻 -是我 是我
- Who's a mob wife? - I'm a mob wife.
不好意思 我听不清
I'm sorry. I couldn't hear you.
我是暴徒之妻
I'm a mob wife.
好吧 佩珀
Okay, um...Pepper,
这事儿由我开口实在有点尴尬
this is a little embarrassing.
我一点都不想听
I don't even want to hear it.
卡梅隆对你还是有感觉
Cameron still has feelings for you.
继续忽悠
Go on.
只是 只是对他来说很困难
Yeah, and it's just -- it's very hard for him
要面对你 尤其还是
to be around you, especially at your...
在你那美妙的早午餐派对 你是
magical brunches where you're just --
你是那么地有魅力
you're -- you're so... magnetic.
而且 我看到他深情凝望你的方式
And then I see the way that he looks at you, and...
该死 我都快被醋淹死了！！！
damn it, pe-- it just makes me so mad
我只能...
That I could just...
是吗
Really?
是呀 你根本不能理解这种情伤 小卡
Yeah, oh, you don't know the pain, Cam!
哦 兄弟们
Ohh, boys!
兄弟们 我真的不想当小三
Boys, I can't stand that I'm coming between you!
我就知道我的魅力让人无法忘却
Not that I'm surprised.
我确实注意到你对我暗送秋波
I admit I have noticed the stolen glances
还有你眼中那森森的渴望
and the yearning in your eyes.
如果我们推掉了你以后的早午餐聚会
Okay. Well, y-you'll forgive us, Pepper,
那佩珀你必须原谅我们
if we sit out your next few brunches?
当然了
Absolutely.
你们不能来真是太遗憾了
I would hate to lose you two.
我会一直把你们当成我的
I've always thought of you as being like my
-儿子们 -儿子们
- Sons? - Sons?
什么"儿子们"
"Sons"?
我本来想说"兄弟"来着
I was gonna say "Brothers."
这房子简直就是一个大茶几
it's like a house of pain!
-好了 克莱尔 -准备
- All right, Claire. - Okay, ready?
-准备好了吗 -我好了
- You ready? - I'm ready.
-好了 说"开始"我们一起使劲 -好的 开始
- All right, on "Go." - Okay, go.
-好了 开始 -加油 用力
- All right? Go! - Okay, go!
加油 加油
Go! Go!
-克莱尔 -天呐 这门有反应了
- Claire! - Oh, god, I got it!
哦 门开了 门真的开了
Ohh! It's moving! It did it!
搞定了 我们做到了
All right! We got it.
-天呐 感谢上帝 -出去吧
- Oh! Thank god! - Go.
天呐 真是感谢各路神佛保佑
Oh, thank god. Thank god. Thank god.
菲尔
Phil?
亲爱的 菲尔 你跑哪儿去了
Honey -- Phil, where are you?
菲尔
Phil...
你想害死老娘吗
Are you kidding me?!
饶了我吧 菲尔
Not the -- Phil!
-菲尔 -老婆
- Phil! - Hey!
你这算怎么回事 人间蒸发了二十分钟
What happened to you? You disappeared for 20 minutes.
我们好不容易才从那间浴室出来
We just had to break ourselves out of that bathroom.
你终于出来了 过来抱抱
I am so happy to see you. Get in here.
不要 不要 不要 你给我正经点
Oh, no. No, no. Seriously.
到底咋回事
What happened?
老爸刚才忙翻了
Dad was incredible!
他忙着关煤气阀门啊
He was running around here turning off the gas line,
清理玻璃渣啊
cleaning up broken glass,
在卢克脑袋撞到墙之后照顾他啊
and taking care of Luke after he ran into a wall.
什么
What?
柜子差点倒下来 实在是吓到我了
I got scared because the cabinet didn't fall down.
哦 对不起
Ohh. I'm sorry.
-没事 别介意 -不 是我不好
- Well, don't worry about it. - No, I'm sorry.
我神经过敏了
Oh... I was so nervous.
我刚才给吓坏了
I freaked out.
没关系 没关系
It's all right. It's all right.
-这真是个杯具的早晨 -是啊
- I think it was a little bit of a rough morning. - Yes.
-是不 -是啊是啊
- Wasn't it? - Yes, it was.
你们想干啥我不管
I don't know about you guys,
我现在只想翘个二郎腿好好休息一下
but I just want to relax and put my feet up.
去"宽容博物馆"休息更好 谁想跟我一起
At the Museum of Tolerance. Who's in?
我呀
I am!
好闺女 咱们走着
You are. Okay. Let's do it.
地震并没什么难以理解的
There's nothing mystical about an earthquake.
只是地壳需要释放其累积过大的压力
Pressure builds, and it's released.
你只要祈祷没有造成太大伤害就好
And you just hope there's not too much damage.
但是地震使你意识到什么最重要
But it makes you realize what matters.
对我来说 是我的家人
And for me, that's my family.
我会帮你向上帝美言几句
I'll put in a good word for you.
好儿子 你最棒了
You're the best, kid.
我的家人和我的高尔夫
My family and golf.
如果天堂真的在天上
If heaven's in the sky,
那我们如何立足呢
what do you walk on?
曼尼 表犯傻了 当然是腾云驾雾啊
Ay, Manny, don't be ridiculous. The clouds.
这说不通啊 云彩只是水蒸气
That makes no sense. Clouds are air.
你会从上面摔下去的
You'd fall right through them.
天堂滴云彩就像蹦床一样
The clouds in heaven -- they're like trampolines.
我可不喜欢蹦床
Mm, I don't like trampolines.
我一跳就觉得像晕船
They make me seasick.
曼尼 表瞎操心了
Manny, stop worrying.
天堂可是灰常美丽滴
Heaven is a beautiful place
有阳光 有彩虹 还有蝴蝶翩翩起舞
with sunshine and rainbows and butterflies.
-神马 有蝴蝶 -哎 米有米有米有
- Butterflies?! -Ay, no, no, no, no.
偶没说蝴蝶 曼尼 那里米有蝴蝶
Aah! I didn't say butterflies! Manny, there's no butterflies!